{"data":[{"question":"You'd like to go, ______ you?","a":"didn't","b":"wouldn't","c":"would","d":"won't","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+Positive statement, nagative tag? \n+ Nagative statement, positive tag? \n+If a modal (can, could, will, should, etc.) is used in the statement, then the same modal is used in the tag part ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She hasn't done it yet, ______ she?","a":"are","b":"hasn't","c":"has","d":"does","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You don't mind if I go, ______ you?","a":"don't","b":"aren't","c":"do","d":"are","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"_______.","a":"I am 15 years old","b":"I am 15 years","c":"I have 15 years","d":"I have 15 years old","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use \" Subject + to be + number + year(s) old\" to introduce number of age","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She died at the ______ 90.","a":"years of","b":"years","c":"age","d":"age of","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use \" at the age of + number\" to mention the particular year-old ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She isn't very clever, _______ she?","a":"doesn't","b":"isn't","c":"does","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You wouldn't do it, ______ you?","a":"would","b":"wouldn't","c":"do","d":"don't","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n+ If a modal (can, could, will, should, etc.) is used in the statement, then the same modal is used in the tag part","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You wanted to go, _______ you?","a":"do","b":"did","c":"didn't","d":"aren't","answer":"3","explain":"- Tag question structure:\u00a0\n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the statement doesn't use an auxiliary verb, then the auxiliary do is used in the tag part","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She hasn't done it yet, _______ she?","a":"has","b":"hasn't","c":"docs","d":"will","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She can help us ,______ she?","a":"can","b":"can't","c":"won't","d":"doesn't","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n+ If a modal (can, could, will, should, etc.) is used in the statement, then the same modal is used in the tag part","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}